Wow, that's amazing!
(Leonard:)I'm in a pretty great mood
today myself.
(Sheldon:)Okay. Guess we're gonna
talk about you now.
(Leonard:)Well, we are, because
Dr. Gallo made me realize
(Leonard:)that I'm a worthwhile person
and that my feelings matter.
(Raj:)I learned that for free from
a cat poster, but good for you.
(Sheldon:)Okay, back to me.
(Sheldon:)I discovered an asteroid,
and now I get to name it.
(Raj:)Wait, what happened to us?
(Sheldon:)Now, this isn't about us,
(Sheldon:)this is about what's best
for the asteroid.
(Leonard:)What are you thinking
of naming it?
(Sheldon:)I haven't settled
on anything yet.
We haven't settled
(Sheldon:)All right, way to go,
Cat Poster. You hang in there.
(Leonard:)You know what'd be nice?
Name it after your girlfriends.
(Leonard:)Show them how much you care.
(Raj:)That is a great idea.
(Sheldon:)It's perfect.
(Sheldon:)It appears romantic,
but it's really just
(Sheldon:)a rock in space that gets me
(Sheldon:)out of Valentine's Day
forever.
(Raj:)So, uh, what were you thinking?
Combine their names?
(Sheldon:)I like it.